```json
{
  "1": "Yuvraj, from QState, reached out to Sheldon at 21st Century Healthcare, Inc. to discuss AI automation for manufacturing efficiency. Sheldon expressed interest and requested more information about QState. Yuvraj provided a document with more information about QState and its capabilities. Sheldon requested clarification on the document's effectiveness and asked for a call to discuss his specific needs. Yuvraj agreed to schedule a call and asked Sheldon for his availability. Sheldon requested to discuss the information after a week or two. The follow-up will be postponed.",
  "3": "Yuvraj, from QState, reached out to Nagaraj Nippu at All Points North to discuss AI automation for mental health care. Nagaraj Nippu expressed interest and requested more information. Yuvraj provided a document with more information about QState and its solutions. Nagaraj Nippu asked about the mode of conversation and requested a call to discuss the information. Yuvraj agreed to schedule a call and asked Nagaraj Nippu for his availability. Nagaraj Nippu requested to be contacted next month or 3 weeks later due to a current project. The follow-up will be postponed."
}
```

```json
{
  "4": "Yuvraj, from QState, reached out to Chari at Alterg Inc. to discuss AI automation for enhanced efficiency. Chari expressed interest and requested more information. Yuvraj provided a document with more information about AI automation and its potential benefits for Alterg. Chari asked about the mode of conversation and requested a call to discuss the information. Yuvraj agreed to schedule a call and asked Chari for his availability. Chari requested a meeting on Saturday at 4 pm.",
  "Last message received on: Fri, 1 Nov 2024 13:07:40 +0530"
}
```

```json
{
  "2": "Dear Thomas,\n\nThank you for your interest in QState's AI automation solutions. We understand that you are currently not interested in our services. We appreciate your time and consideration. Please feel free to reach out if you have any further questions or if your needs change in the future.\n\nSincerely,\nYuvraj"
}
```
